Guide to the Rice University Past Faculty and Staff records, 1961-1996 UA 008
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas
Rice University Past faculty and staff records
1915-2013
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas https://library.rice.edu/woodson
Rice University
UA 008
43 Linear Feet (43 boxes)
Correspondence, memoranda, and reports relating to faculty and professional employees no longer associated with Rice University. Includes permanent and temporary appointments.
Biographical / Historical
Rice University opened in October 1912 as the Rice Institute.
Scope and Contents
Correspondence, memoranda, and reports relating to faculty and professional employees no longer associated with Rice University. Includes permanent and temporary appointments.
Access Restrictions
This material is restricted. Permission to access these records must be obtained from the Rice University President's office.
Conditions Governing Access
Stored off-site at the Library Service Center. Please request this material via woodson@rice.edu or call 713-348-2586.
Acquisition Information
This material was transferred to Woodson Research Center in 1968; 1989-90; July, 1991; July, 1992; and June, 1996.
Index Terms
Subjects
Universities and colleges; Faculty
Document Types
letters (correspondence); memorandums
- Series I: Past Faculty and Staff A-Z, 1915-2003, 119315
  General Note
  The date on each file is for the time that the individual worked at Rice. The date does not always represent the date of the documents inside each file.
  - Abernathy, George R. - History, 1967; 167092 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Abbott, William Wright - History, 1960-1962; 167093 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Adams, John Q. - Education, 1964-1965; 167094 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Adams, Capt. Thomas M. - Military Science, 1978-1981; 167095 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Adler, Paul - Chemical Engineering, 1979-1980; 167096 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Afriat, Sydney Napthali - Economics, 1963-1965; 167097 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Aghili, Hafez - Chemical Engineering, 1979-1983; 167098 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Agmon, Shmuel - Mathematics, 1949-1952, 1964-1965; 167099 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Alexandropoulos, Nikos G. - Mechanical Engineering, 1974-1976; 167100 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Alphin, Capt. Arthur B. - History, 1979-1980; 167101 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Alvarez, Roy R. - Military Science, 1974-1975; 167102 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Anderson, D. Kent - Jones School of Administration, 1980-1982; 167103 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Anderson, Hugh R. - Space Science, 1965; 167104 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Anderson, Michael T. - Mathematics, 1981-1984; 167105 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Anderson, Roger B. - Classics, 1969-1973; 167106 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Angene, Lyle E. - Philosophy, 1971-1978; 167107 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Ansevin, Krystyna - Biology, 1965-1980; 167108 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Anstrand, David E. - Architecture, 1975-1978; 167109 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Antsaklis, Panayotis John - Electrical Engineering, 1977-1978; 167110 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Antunes, George - Political Science, 1969-1974; 167111 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Archer, David A. - Mathematical Sciences, 1978-1979; 167112 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Arculus, Richard John - Geology, 1975-1977; 167113 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Arnold, Jeanne E. - Anthropology, 1980-1981; 167114 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Arnold, Robert Glen - Electrical Engineering, 1983; 167115 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Aronson, Donald G. - Mathematics, 1974-1975; 167116 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Asimow, Robert W. - Mechanical Engineering, 1961-1964; 167117 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Atkinson, Bernard - Chemical Engineering, 1962-1963; 167118 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Austin, William H. - Philosophy, 1963-1972; 167119 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Auten, John H. - Economics, 1953-1965; 167120 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Axelsson, Owe - Geology, 1983; 167121 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Backus, Kerby D. - Civil Engineering, 1957-1963; 167122 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Badner, Carol Luce - Art, 1977-1979; 167123 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Badner, Mino David - Fine Arts, 1968-1977; 167124 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Bagby, S. Thomas - Mathematics, 1981; 167125 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Bahler, Alan S. - Electrical Engineering, 1966-1968; 167126 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Bailey, Edward T. - Military Science, 1980-1983; 167127 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Bailey, William T. - Jones School of Administration, 1981-1982; 167128 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Baker, Lee Edward - Electrical Engineering, 1955-1963; 167129 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Baker, Stewart A. - English, 1964-1980; 167130 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Baker, Walter Searls, Jr. - Business Administration, 1962-1963; 167131 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Bakuzis, Peter - Chemistry, 1977-1978; 167132 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Bale, Allen M. - Director of Athletics, 1948-1979; 167133 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Ballas, George - Jones School of Administration, 1978-1983; 167134 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Ballentine, John Gregory - Economics, 1973; 167135 (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Ballonoff, Paul - Mathematical Sciences, 1975-1976; 167136 (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Ballonoff, Paul Allen - Anthropology, 1972-1974; 167137 (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - Bannister, Ronald J. - Accounting, 1965; 167138 (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - Barber, William D. - History, 1961-1966; 167139 (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - Barnard, Anthony Charles Langrish - Physics, 1961-1967; 167140 (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - Barnard, William - Music, 1979-1985; 167141 (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - Barney, Harry I. - Health and Physical Education, 1972-1973; 167142 (Box 1, Folder 51)
  - Barratt, Ernest Stoelting - Psychology, 1965-1966; 167143 (Box 1, Folder 52)
  - Barthelme, Donald - Architecture, 1959-1961; 167144 (Box 1, Folder 53)
  - Bartholomew, Barbara Gray - English, 1963-1967; 167145 (Box 1, Folder 54)
  - Bartlett, John - Architecture, 1974-1980; 167146 (Box 1, Folder 55)
  - Bartoszynski, Robert - Mathematical Sciences, 1979-1983; 167147 (Box 1, Folder 56)
  - Batson, Bartus H. - Electrical Engineering, 1975-1976; 167149 (Box 1, Folder 57)
  - Barten, George W., Jr. - Mathematics, 1966; 167150 (Box 1, Folder 58)
  - Battestin, Martin C. - English, 1966-1967; 167151 (Box 1, Folder 59)
  - Bauer, Friedrich-Wilhelm - Mathematics, 1967-1968; 167152 (Box 1, Folder 60)
  - Baumslag, Gilbert - Mathematics, 1968-1973; 167153 (Box 1, Folder 61)
  - Bayazitoglu, Yildirim Omer - Mechanical Engineering, 1978-1979; 167154 (Box 1, Folder 62)
  - Bayne, Donald S. - Fine Arts, 1974-1975; 167155 (Box 1, Folder 63)
  - Beal, Rebecca - English, 1982-1983; 167156 (Box 1, Folder 64)
  - Beale, Alan R. - Mathematics, 1979-1980; 167157 (Box 1, Folder 65)
  - Beam, John E. - Physics, 1967-1973; 167158 (Box 1, Folder 66)
  - Beatrous, Frank H., Jr. - Mathematics, 1978-1980; 167159 (Box 1, Folder 67)
  - Bell, Robert L, Jr. - Psychology, 1973-1981; 167160 (Box 1, Folder 68)
  - Bencivenga, Ermano - Philosophy, 1978-1979; 167161 (Box 1, Folder 69)
  - Bender, Stephen O. - Architecture, 1973-1976; 167162 (Box 1, Folder 70)
  - Bennett, Harry - History, 1962-1963; 167163 (Box 1, Folder 71)
  - Berkman, Larry - Architecture, 1979-1980; 167164 (Box 1, Folder 72)
  - Berthier, Anne Marie Francoise - Mathematics, 1977-1979; 167165 (Box 1, Folder 73)
  - Besen, Stanley M. - Economics, 1965-1980; 167166 (Box 1, Folder 74)
  - Bezman, Michel - Architecture, 1975; 167167 (Box 1, Folder 75)
  - Bible, Frances - Music, 1978-1990; 167168 (Box 1, Folder 76)
  - Biehl, Kathy Anne - Political Science, 1982-1983; 167169 (Box 1, Folder 77)
  - Bishop, Morris G. - French, 1966; 167170 (Box 1, Folder 78)
  - Bishop, Col. Raymond C. - Military Science, 1970-1973; 167171 (Box 1, Folder 79)
  - Bivens, Irl Crawford - Mathematics, 1980-1982; 167172 (Box 1, Folder 80)
  - Black, Hugh C. - Fine Arts, 1949-1962; 167173 (Box 1, Folder 81)
  - Blanton, Richard E. - Anthropology, 1970-1973; 167174 (Box 1, Folder 82)
  - Blazey, Keith William - Physics, 1980; 167175 (Box 1, Folder 83)
  - Bloch, Felix - Physics, 1963; 167176 (Box 1, Folder 84)
  - Bloom, Joe M. - Psychology, 1966-1967; 167177 (Box 1, Folder 85)
  - Bochner, Salomon - Mathematics, 1968-1982; 167178 (Box 1, Folder 86)
  - Boewe, Karl-Heinz W. - Germanics, 1967-1968; 167179 (Box 1, Folder 87)
  - Bolling, Emma Dominy - Education, 1965-1968; 167180 (Box 1, Folder 88)
  - Bonner, Tom - Physics, 1931-1961; 167181 (Box 1, Folder 89)
  - Booker, John D. - Chemical Engineering, 1979-1980; 167182 (Box 1, Folder 90)
  - Bosarge, W. Edwin, Jr. - Mathematical Sciences, 1969-1974; 167183 (Box 1, Folder 91)
  - Boterf, Chester - Fine Arts, 1973-1993; 167184 (Box 1, Folder 92)
  - Bourland, Hardy M. - Electrical Engineering, 1961-1980; 167185 (Box 1, Folder 93)
  - Bourne, Henry Clark, Jr. - Electrical Engineering, 1963-1979; 167186 (Box 1, Folder 94)
  - Bowen, Ray M. - Mechanical Engineering, 1968-1983; 167187 (Box 1, Folder 95)
  - Boyer, Anne-Marie - French, 1962-1963; 167188 (Box 1, Folder 96)
  - Brackett, Thomas E. - Chemistry, 1963; 167189 (Box 1, Folder 97)
  - Brams, Patricia - Sociology, 1979-1980; 167190 (Box 1, Folder 98)
  - Bramlett, Mead R. - Military Science, 1964-1967; 167191 (Box 1, Folder 99)
  - Brewer, Rose - Sociology, 1974-1977; 167193 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Brinkman, Hans-Berndt - Mathematics, 1965-1966; 167194 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Brockmann, Jan - German, 1964-1965; 167195 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Brothers, Dwight Stanley - Economics, 1956-1967; 167196 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Brown, A. H. - Mathematics, 1962-1963; 167197 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Brown, Carradean L. - Naval Science, 1977-1979; 167198 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Brown, Christopher J. - Architecture, 1973-1982; 167199 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Brown, Eric Ramsay - Jones Graduate School of Administration, 1977-1980; 167200 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Brown, Robert Theodore - Space Science, 1966-1968; 167201 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Brown, Stephen L. - Health and Physical Education, 1980-1982; 167202 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Bryan, Andrew Bonnell - Physics, 1919-1977; 167203 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Buck, Meera - Psychology, 1976-1979; 167204 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Bullard, Robert D. - Sociology, 1979-1980; 167205 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Bultmann, Hermann - Biology, 1971-1978; 167206 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Bunch, Robert G. - Accounting, 1979-1982; 167207 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Burago, Alla - Russian, 1980-1983; 167208 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Burch, Robert W. - Philosophy, 1968-1974; 167209 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Burchfiel, Burrell Clark - Geology, 1962-1978; 167210 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Burghard, Herman C., Jr. - Mechanical Engineering, 1955-1962; 167211 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Burns, Joseph M. - Economics, 1971-1974; 167212 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Burton, Edwin T. - Economics, 1973-1974; 167213 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Busch, Arthur W. - Civil/Environmental Engineering, 1955-1975; 167214 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Bush, George H. W. - Jones Graduate School of Administration, 1977-1981; 167215 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Butler, Richard V. - Economics, 1973-1979; 167216 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Calderon, Calixto P. - Mathematics, 1978-1979; 167217 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Caldwell, Martha Belle - Fine Arts, 1966-1968; 167218 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Calfee, Richard V. - Biomedical/Electrical Engineering, 1977-1981; 167219 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Camblin, Bob - Fine Arts, 1967-1972; 167220 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Camden, Carroll - English, 1930-1974; 167221 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Cameron, Major Dougal M. - Naval Science, 1967; 167222 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Cameron, Douglas MacDonald - Spanish, 1971-1979; 167223 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Campbell, Bonnalie Oetting - Biology, 1979; 167224 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Campbell, Sue Ellen - English, 1978; 167225 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Campise, James A. - Mathematical Sciences, 1973-1979; 167226 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Caples, Cynthia B. - German/Russian, 1972-1976; 167227 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Cargill, Robert L. - Chemistry, 1980-1983; 167228 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Carlton, Mary J. - Health and Physical Education, 1981-1983; 167229 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Carnahan, Norman F. - Chemical Engineering, 1976-1977; 167230 (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Carr, C. Reed - Health and Physical Education, 1975-1979; 167231 (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Carrara, John D., Jr. - Architecture, 1975-1979; 167232 (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Carter, Elmer Buzby - Physics, 1963-1965; 167233 (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - Cassard, Lawrence J. - Psychiatric Services, 1970-1973; 167234 (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - Caudill, William W. - Architecture, 1961-1983; 167235 (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - Cavanaugh, Kevin Paul - Architecture, 1979-1982; 167236 (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - Cech, Irina - Architecture, 1974-1980; 167237 (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - Chalmers, David J. - Chemistry, 1966; 167238 (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - Chambers, Leslie A. - Environmental Sciences and Engineering, 1974-1984; 167239 (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - Chan, Steve T. - Political Science, 1978-1979; 167240 (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - Chapman, Frank M., Jr. - Chemistry, 1973-1974; 167241 (Box 2, Folder 49)
  - Chapou, Marie-France - French, 1967-1968; 167242 (Box 2, Folder 50)
  - Characklis, William G. - Environmental Science and Engineering, 1970-1983; 167243 (Box 2, Folder 51)
  - Charlton, Norman W. - Health and Physical Education, 1964-1973; 167244 (Box 2, Folder 52)
  - Charyn, Jerome - English, 1978-1979; 167245 (Box 2, Folder 53)
  - Cheney, Alan - Fine Arts, 1969-1975; 167246 (Box 2, Folder 54)
  - Cheney, Charles C. - Anthropology, 1979-1981; 167247 (Box 2, Folder 55)
  - Chimosky, John E. - Biomedical Engineering, 1974-1979; 167248 (Box 2, Folder 56)
  - Claborn, Luther - Mathematics, 1967; 167249 (Box 2, Folder 57)
  - Clark, Irwin - Biology, 1962-1963; 167250 (Box 2, Folder 58)
  - Clark, Martha R. - Psychology, 1980-1981; 167251 (Box 2, Folder 59)
  - Clarke, Robert W. - Accounting, 1974-1981; 167252 (Box 2, Folder 60)
  - Clayton, John P. - Religious Studies, 1982-1983; 167255 (Box 2, Folder 61)
  - Cleveland, Sidney E. - Psychology, 1963; 167256 (Box 2, Folder 62)
  - Cohen, James S. - Physics, 1979-1980; 167257 (Box 2, Folder 63)
  - Coleman, H. Howard - Electrical Engineering, 1979-1980; 167258 (Box 2, Folder 64)
  - Collins, Michael G. - Mathematical Sciences, 1979-1980; 167259 (Box 2, Folder 65)
  - Colson, Anthony C. - Anthropology, 1977; 167260 (Box 2, Folder 66)
  - Conant, Ralph W. - Architecture, 1969-1974; 167261 (Box 2, Folder 67)
  - Conlisk, John - Economics, 1964-1966; 167262 (Box 2, Folder 68)
  - Conner, Jack Edward - English, 1954-1962; 167263 (Box 2, Folder 69)
  - Conover, Albert P. - Head Football Coach, 1973-1975; 167264 (Box 2, Folder 70)
  - Cook, Richard - Space Science, 1963-1965; 167265 (Box 2, Folder 71)
  - Cooke, Timothy W. - Economics, 1979-1984; 167266 (Box 2, Folder 72)
  - Coombs, Robert John - Jones Graduate School of Administration, 1980-1981; 167267 (Box 2, Folder 73)
  - Cooper, Robin D. G. - Chemistry, 1977; 167268 (Box 2, Folder 74)
  - Courtine, Francoise G. - French, 1963-1966; 167269 (Box 2, Folder 75)
  - Courtney, Susan - Health and Physical Education, 1972-1973; 167270 (Box 2, Folder 76)
  - Covo, Mario Mino - Economics, 1982-1984; 167271 (Box 2, Folder 77)
  - Crane, David A. - Architecture, 1972-1982; 167272 (Box 2, Folder 78)
  - Crosman, Robert T. - English, 1982-1983; 167273 (Box 2, Folder 79)
  - Crouse, Harold Dean - Education, 1963-1964; 167274 (Box 2, Folder 80)
  - Crouse, Wayne T. - Shepherd School of Music, 1975-1983; 167275 (Box 2, Folder 81)
  - Culler, Marc - Mathematics, 1979-1983; 167276 (Box 2, Folder 82)
  - Curry, Brian - Health and Physical Education, 1973-1975; 167277 (Box 2, Folder 83)
  - Curtis, Howard B. - Mathematics, 1955-1956, 1963-1964; 167278 (Box 2, Folder 84)
  - Curtis, Jerry Lynn - French, 1968-1975; 167279 (Box 2, Folder 85)
  - Cushman, Richard D. - Anthropology, 1974-1981; 167280 (Box 2, Folder 86)
  - Cyprus, Joel - Electrical Engineering, 1966-1973; 167281 (Box 2, Folder 87)
  - Dadok, Jiri - Mathematics, 1977-1980, 1983-1984; 167427 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Dale, Denver T. - Naval Science, 1973-1975; 167428 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Danishefsky, Samuel - Chemistry, 1977; 167429 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Danner, Ernie L. - Jones Graduate School of Administration, 1981-1983; 167430 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Daugherty, Beth R. - English, 1981; 167431 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Davidson, David L. - Mechanical Engineering and Materials Science, 1978; 167432 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Davidson, Frederic M. - Electrical Engineering, 1979-1980; 167433 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Davidson, John Michael - Chemical Engineering, 1978; 167434 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Davidson, Walter D. - Naval Science, 1971; 167435 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Davies, Joseph Ilott - Biology, 1929-1966; 167436 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Davis, Wayne A. - Philosophy, 1977-1978; 167437 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Davis, William B. - Environmental Engineering, 1971-1972; 167438 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Dawkins, George Spangler - Chemical Engineering, 1961-1964; 167439 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Deans, Harry Alexander - Chemical Engineering, 1959-1983; 167440 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Deck, Warren P. - Shepherd School of Music, 1977-1979; 167441 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Deegan, John, Jr. - Political Science, 1972-1975; 167442 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - de Montricher, Gilbert M. - Mathematical Sciences, 1978-1980; 167443 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Denny, Vernon E. - Chemical Engineering, 1957-1964; 167444 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - DeSantis, Capt. Albert A., Jr. - Naval Science, 1976-1979; 167445 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Detweiler, Philip Franklin - History, 1963-1965; 167446 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - de Vecsey, Esther B. - Art and Art History and Gallery Director, 1980-1983; 167447 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Devereaux, Mary L. - Philosophy, 1981-1983; 167448 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - de Vries, Nick Johannes - Fine Arts, 1973-1974; 167449 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - DeZurko, Edward R. - Fine Arts, 1947-1962; 167450 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Di Corcia, Joseph W. - History, 1973-1975; 167451 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Dippolito, Paul Randall - Mathematics, 1975-1977; 167452 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Dispert, Helmut Hans - Chemistry, 1978-1979; 167453 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Dobrovsky, Sergei - Economics, 1963-1964; 167454 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Doering, William von Eggers - Chemistry, 1978-1979; 167455 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Donnelly, Thomas Wallace - Geology, 1959-1966; 167456 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Donoho, Paul Leighton - Physics, 1959-1979; 167457 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Doran, Charles Francis - Political Science, 1970-1979; 167458 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Dorfman, Peter W. - Psychology, 1974-1978; 167459 (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Dorman, H. James - Geology, 1974-1978; 167460 (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - Douglas, Jim, Jr. - Mathematics, 1949-1967; 167461 (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - Douglass, H. Robert - Architecture, 1973-1980; 167462 (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - DuCharme, Wesley M. - Psychology, 1968-1974; 167463 (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - Dugundji, James - Mathematics, 1967-1968; 167464 (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - Dunaway, James Karl - Architecture, 1962-1967; 167465 (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - Dunbar, William D. - Mathematics, 1981-1984; 167466 (Box 3, Folder 40)
  - Duncan, Hugh Dalziel - Sociology (photograph), 1962-1963; 167467 (Box 3, Folder 41)
  - Duployé, Gustave Marie - French, 1969-1976; 167468 (Box 3, Folder 42)
  - Durst, Lincoln Kearney - Mathematics, 1955-1967; 167469 (Box 3, Folder 43)
  - Dvoretzky, Edward - German, 1959; 167470 (Box 3, Folder 44)
  - Dwyer, A. W. Thomas, III - Electrical Engineering, 1979-1980; 167471 (Box 3, Folder 45)
  - Dyer, Eldon - Mathematics, 1964-1966; 167472 (Box 3, Folder 46)
  - Dyer, James C., IV - Economics/Accounting, 1975-1979; 167473 (Box 3, Folder 47)
  - Dyess, Arthur D., Jr. - Architecture, 1955-1973; 167474 (Box 3, Folder 48)
  - Easley, Grady M. - Mathematical Sciences, 1979-1980; 167475 (Box 3, Folder 49)
  - Edelstein, Mozelle - Shepherd School of Music, 1971-1977; 167476 (Box 3, Folder 50)
  - Edwards, Edgar Owen - Administration, 1977-1982; 167477 (Box 3, Folder 51)
  - Edwards, Victor H. - Environmental Science and Engineering, 1979-1980; 167478 (Box 3, Folder 52)
  - Elliot, Douglas G. - Chemical Engineering, 1977-1979; 167479 (Box 3, Folder 53)
  - Ellis, James E. - Geology, 1982; 167480 (Box 3, Folder 54)
  - Elman, Richard S. - Mathematics, 1972-1976; 167481 (Box 3, Folder 55)
  - Emanuel, Victor Lloyd - Political Science, 1972-1974; 167482 (Box 3, Folder 56)
  - Emery, Frank E. - Electrical Engineering, 1960-1964; 167483 (Box 3, Folder 57)
  - Enders, Allen C. - Biology, 1956-1963; 167484 (Box 3, Folder 58)
  - Endo, Akira - Shepherd School of Music, 1979; 167485 (Box 3, Folder 59)
  - Engel, Frederic Andre - Anthropology, 1976-1978; 167486 (Box 3, Folder 60)
  - Englert, Geroge Philip - Architecture, 1962-1963; 167487 (Box 3, Folder 61)
  - Ereli, Eliezer - Jones School of Administration, 1977-1978; 167488 (Box 3, Folder 62)
  - Erdman, Donelly - Architecture, 1969-1975; 167489 (Box 3, Folder 63)
  - Eris, Ibrahim - Economics, 1970-1973; 167490 (Box 3, Folder 64)
  - Erwin, Stuart M. - Shepherd School of Music, 1979-1980; 167491 (Box 3, Folder 65)
  - Eskin, Arnold - Biology, 1972-1978; 167492 (Box 3, Folder 66)
  - Ettelson, Meryl - Shepherd School of Music, 1976-1983; 167493 (Box 3, Folder 67)
  - Ettlinger, Martin Grossman - Chemistry, 1952-1964; 167494 (Box 3, Folder 68)
  - Ewing, Maurice - Geology, 1972-1975; 167495 (Box 3, Folder 69)
  - Ewing, Ralph E. - Mathematical Sciences, 1980-1983; 167496 (Box 3, Folder 70)
  - Ewton, Ralph W., Jr. - Germanics, 1965; 167497 (Box 3, Folder 71)
  - Fabes, Eugene B. - Mathematics, 1965-1967; 167498 (Box 3, Folder 72)
  - Fahrenthold, Eric P. - Mechanical Engineering and Materials Science, 1983-1984; 167499 (Box 3, Folder 73)
  - Fairweather, Graeme - Mathematics, 1966-1967; 167500 (Box 3, Folder 74)
  - Farnsworth, Jacqueline B. - Psychology, 1978-1979; 167501 (Box 3, Folder 75)
  - Fedyshyn, Oleh S. - Political Science, 1964-1967; 167502 (Box 3, Folder 76)
  - Fegan, Howard S. - Mathematics, 1978-1980; 167503 (Box 3, Folder 77)
  - Felkin, Hugh Nigel - Chemistry, 1979; 167504 (Box 3, Folder 78)
  - Ferber, Howard - Art and Art History, 1979; 167505 (Box 3, Folder 79)
  - Feustel, Edward A. - Computer Science, 1968-1980; 167506 (Box 3, Folder 80)
  - Fishbein, Leslie - History, 1975-1976; 167507 (Box 3, Folder 81)
  - Forbes, M. C. - Environmental Science and Engineering, 1972-1973; 167508 (Box 3, Folder 82)
  - Forough, Ali - Shepherd School of Music, 1979-1981; 167509 (Box 3, Folder 83)
  - Forthofer, Ronald N. - Mathematical Sciences, 1974-1981; 167510 (Box 3, Folder 84)
  - France, Newell Edwin - Architecture, 1970-1980; 167557 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Francis, Capt. Duncan F. - Naval Science, 1962-1966; 167558 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Frank, Robert H. - History, 1965-1966; 167559 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Franklin, Jack L. - Sociology, 1981-1982; 167560 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Franklin, Joseph L. - Chemistry, 1963-1982; 167561 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Frederickson, George M. - History, 1983; 167562 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Freeman, Michael B. - Mathematics, 1979-1980; 167563 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Freund, Max - German, 1925-1980; 167564 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Friedlander, Lee - Art and Art History, 1977; 167565 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Fuguitt, Diana Lee - Economics, 1981-1982; 167566 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Fulton, James Street - Philosophy, 1946-1974; 167567 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Furino, Valeria B. - Spanish, 1964-1965; 167568 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Furse, Margaret L. - Religious Studies, 1970-1973; 167569 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Gaier, Ulrich - German and Russian, 1972-1973; 167570 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Gallaher, Art, Jr. - Anthropology and Sociology, 1961-1962; 167571 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Gallegly, Joseph Stephen, Jr. - English, 1922-1982; 167572 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Gamst, Frederick C. - Anthropology, 1966-1975; 167573 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Gansow, Otto A. - Chemistry, 1968-1973; 167574 (Box 4, Folder 18)